(Bernadette:)All right. Here you go.
(Bernadette:)Two lemonades,
(Bernadette:)one iced tea
(Bernadette:)and a root beer for Priya.
- Is it diet?
- That's what you ordered.
(Priya:)Thank you.
(Priya:)Hey, have you and Howard
(Priya:)started planning
your wedding yet?
(Bernadette:)Yeah. We're thinking
of having it on a cliff
(Bernadette:)overlooking the ocean.
(Howard:)Nothing soothes
those pre-wedding jitters
(Howard:)like the thought
of falling and drowning.
(Leonard:)What did your mother say
(Leonard:)when you told her you were
getting married?
(Bernadette:)He hasn't told her yet.
(Bernadette:)He's waiting for
the right time.
(Howard:)I was thinking of weaving
it into her eulogy.
(Priya:)Howard, you've got
to tell your mother.
(Howard:)Hey, have you told your parents
you're dating
(Howard:)this short glass
of skim milk here?
(Priya:)Uh... that's different.
(Priya:)First of all,
we're not engaged;
(Priya:)and second,
Indian parents
(Priya:)are very protective
of their children.
(Howard:)Right, right,
whereas Jewish mothers
(Howard:)take a casual, la-di-da
approach to their sons.